<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<chapter id="ch.intro"
         version="5.0"
         xsi:schemaLocation="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook http://www.docbook.org/xml/5.0/xsd/docbook.xsd http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink http://www.docbook.org/xml/5.0/xsd/xlink.xsd"
         xml:base="../" xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
         xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
         xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" xmlns:ns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook">

    <title>Introduction</title>
  
    <para>This chapter introduces the modules in charge of the BPM functionality inside the Kie Workbench. 
        These modules were grouped under the name of JBPM Console NG and they can be found here:  http://github.com/droolsjbpm/jbpm-console-ng .
        Inside the GitHub repository will also find a standalone version of these modules integrated with some authoring tools,
        like for example the Process Designer and the Form Designer, as well as some common tooling to explore the business repositories. 
        
        If you are interested in a full integrated environment that provides  Form Modeling, Data Modeling, Rules Authoring, etc, you should take a 
        look at Kie Workbench which provides all the functionality discrived in these docs plus all the mentioned above.
        
    </para>
  
    <section>    
        <title>Documentation Sections</title>
        <para>This documentation is organized into different sections that reflect the project internal structure. 
            The main goal of this document is to explain the functional aspects of each of the following modules as well as
            to server as reference for developers that wants to customize or extend the provided functionalities. </para>

        <orderedlist>
            <listitem>
                <para>Process Runtime: This module contains all the tools to create and manage 
                    process definitions and process instances.</para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
                <para>Tasks: This module provides all the Human Tasks related functionality. This module is integrated with the 
                Form Modeller to provide a unified experience, so users can work on the tasks that are assigned to them.</para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
                <para>Deployments: This module contains all the functionality related with the management of deployment units, that
                represent packaged business assets ready to use in runtime environments.</para>
            </listitem>
      
            <listitem>
                <para>Jobs: This module provides all the functionality to schedule async Jobs using the jBPM Executor module.</para>
            </listitem>
        </orderedlist>
  
        <para>Notice that on these documents the common infrastructure screens are not explained. 
            If you are interested in finding more information about Process Designer, Project Explorer, Form Modeller and other modules
        please check the jBPM Documentation. </para>
  
    </section>
</chapter>
